#### Contact

7194532532 (Home) kennethscribner@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kenneth-scribner-076a8317 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Nursing
ACLS
Critical Care

# Kenneth Scribner

Unit Manager at Life Care Centers of America Aurora, Colorado

# Summary

Currently Unit Manager at Life Care Center of Littleton, Co. Registered Nurse since 2009. I have twenty-eight years of experience in the medical field. From military medic, LVN, Supervisor of clinics, to CCT Nurse. Primary an Emergency Department Nurse, but I have worked on medical, surgical, ICU and mental health units. I have worked in immunizations, family practice, wound care, orthopedics, neurology, surgery, ENT, GI, and urology clinics. I have even done correctional health care and home health. Great addition for any company that is in need of a seasoned and professional nurse who cares about the welfare of his patients. I just finished my BSN and I am now working on my FNP. Have to stay in Colorado for another year and then I would like to get back into travel nursing. Thank you for looking at my profile.

# Experience

Life Care Centers of America Unit Manager December 2019 - Present (7 months) Littleton, CO

Medical Staffing Network
Travel Registered Nurse
November 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Denver, Colorado

Republic Health Resources
Travel Nurse
November 2015 - Present (4 years 8 months)

Medical Solutions
Travel RN
May 2015 - Present (5 years 2 months)

### Integrated Healthcare Solutions

4 years 6 months

### Registered Nurse

November 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Greater Denver Area

#### Travel RN

July 2015 - December 2019 (4 years 6 months)

#### Park Forest Care

RN

March 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Westminster, Colorado

Night Charge Nurse

### Dignity Health

Charge Nurse

November 2010 - May 2015 (4 years 7 months)

# Kaiser Permanente

ED RN (level 2 trauma)

April 2014 - September 2014 (6 months)

Sacramento, California

# ProTransport-1

**CCT Nurse** 

November 2013 - March 2014 (5 months)

Sacramento, California Area

#### Nursefinders

Per Diem RN and LVN

August 2001 - March 2011 (9 years 8 months)

Fountain Valley, California

Per Diem at Solano County Jail, Sutter Delta, Sutter Solano, Mercy Methodist,

Kaiser Vallejo, and North Bay Medical Center.

# North Valley Medical Staffing

Travel RN

August 2010 - October 2010 (3 months)

Auburn, California

# Tulare Regional Medical Center

Registered Nurse

September 2009 - September 2010 (1 year 1 month)

Tulare, California

#### Solvere

Registered Nurse

March 2009 - March 2010 (1 year 1 month)

Kern Valley State Prison

# Sutter Regional Medical Fndtn

Supervisor and LVN

March 2006 - August 2008 (2 years 6 months)

Fairfield, California

Worked in the Urgent Clinic and then was promoted to Supervisor of ENT, GI, and Surgery clinics.

### Contra Costa Medical Group

LVN

March 2004 - March 2008 (4 years 1 month)

Martinez, California

Worked in Family practice, Surgery, Wound Care, Orthopedic, and Neurology Clinics.

#### United States Air Force

**TSgt** 

June 1993 - February 2003 (9 years 9 months)

 $\label{thm:medical-surgical} \mbox{Medical-Surgical units},$ 

Immunizations, Dermatology, Emergency, and Aeromedical Staging.

# Education

Chamberlain University

Master's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2019 - 2021)

Chamberlain University

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2019)

Colorado Technical University

BSN · (2017 - 2019)

# Pacific Union College

ASN, Nursing · (2006 - 2009)

# Community College of the Air Force

Associate's degree, Health Services/Allied Health/Health Sciences,

General · (1993 - 2002)